(Howard:)Because you can die that way.
(Raj:)Oh, that would be a good way to go.
(Penny:)-Hi.
-Oh, hey.
(Sheldon:)Good, Penny.
Reminder, bowling tonight at 7:00.
(Penny:)Oh, right. Bowling.
(Leonard:)You don't have to come
if you don't want.
(Penny:)No, no, it's okay. I mean, let's face it,
you would get creamed without me.
(Sheldon:)We would indeed.
In this particular case...
(Sheldon:)...your lack of femininity
works to our advantage.
Yeah. It's always nice chatting with you,
Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)-Sarcasm?
PENNY: Thinly veiled contempt.
-Remember, 7:00.
PENNY: Got it.
(Sheldon:)-Pacific Daylight Time.
PENNY: Bite me.
(Sheldon:)Please reserve that butch spirit
for the lanes.
(Howard:)I thought you were bringing
your own bowling shoes.
(Sheldon:)These are my own bowling shoes.